



# **Aytac Malkoc**

**Date of birth:** 05/03/2000 | **Nationality:** Turkish | **Gender:** Male

Phone number: (+90) 5362681137 (Mobile) | Email address:

aytacmalkoc@protonmail.com | **Twitter:** https://www.x.com/ird aytacmalkoc |

LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/aytacmalkoc">https://www.linkedin.com/in/aytacmalkoc</a> | GitHub:

https://www.github.com/aytacmalkoc

Address: R. Sevket Ince Mahallesi, 1935. Sokak No: 30/7, E-22 Blok, 35540,

Izmir, Türkiye (Home)

## ABOUT ME

I am a passionate software developer specializing in web applications and cross-platform mobile applications. In my projects, I focus on delivering not only user-friendly but also technology-integrated experiences, utilizing technologies such as Laravel, Strapi, Express, Next.JS, React.JS, and React Native. For this reason, I frequently make use of artificial intelligence and third-party tools.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

18/03/2023 - CURRENT Izmir, Türkive

## FRONTEND DEVELOPER ATTELIA HEALTH TOUR

I took part in the development of the websites and applications of Attelia Health Tour company, based in Antalya/Turkey, which provides services in the health tourism and health sector.

**Business or Sector** Human health and social work activities | **Department** Software Team |

Email info@atteliahealthtour.com | Website https://atteliahealthtour.com

08/08/2021 - 31/12/2021 Izmir, Türkiye

FULL STACK DEVELOPER - REMOTE UPPEREARTH DIGITAL

As a full stack developer, I was involved in the development of numerous web applications and API services, primarily using Laravel. I also played a key role in advancing application development processes within our organization.

**Business or Sector** Information and communication | **Department** | T Department |

Email info@upperearthdigital.com | Website https://www.upperearthdigital.com

01/09/2018 - 30/06/2019 Izmir, Türkiye

**INTERN FIKIR ISLER** 

During my internship, I had the opportunity to work on numerous corporate projects and the company's SASS projects. I had the chance to educate myself on developing applications by actively using HTML, CSS, jQuery, Codelgniter, and MySQL technologies.

**Business or Sector** Information and communication | **Department** Development Team |

**Email** <u>izmir@fikirisler.com</u> | **Website** <u>https://www.fikirisler.com</u>

#### EDUCATION AND TRAINING

01/09/2019 - 30/09/2021 Isparta, Türkiye

**UNIVERSITY** Isparta University of Applied Sciences

Website https://www.isparta.edu.tr

01/09/2014 - 06/2019 Izmir, Türkiye

HIGH SCHOOL Mersinli Vocational and Technical Anatolian High School

Website https://mersinlieml.meb.k12.tr/

#### LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): TURKISH

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
ENGLISH	B1	B1	A2	A2	B1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

## DIGITAL SKILLS

Git | GitHub | PHP | React | Next JS | React Native | Laravel | Figma | Asana | MS Office Tools | HTML | CSS | MySQL | Website Programming (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Ajax, AngularJS, Bootstrap) | StrapiJS | Javascript(Nodejs, ExpressJs)

# PROJECTS

18/04/2021 - 21/04/2021

do-todo

Mobile todo application using React Native.

Link https://github.com/aytacmalkoc/do-todo

17/07/2022 - CURRENT

**isondb** 

We may need a lightweight database when developing simple applications. We use local database packages to avoid having to connect to any database. That's why I wanted to develop a JSON database application that works as a key-value. In this way, we can store data with keys as if creating a table in a single database file.

Link https://github.com/aytacmalkoc/jsondb

20/08/2022 - CURRENT

tcmb-exchange-rates-api

This API service provides TCMB's exchange rates data.

Link https://github.com/aytacmalkoc/tcmb-exchange-rates-api

## HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

# **Hobbies & Interests**

- Wood works
- Astronomy
- Game development